⊗ Antonio Rodriguez

Web Development and Digital Marketing Expert

Living in Miami, Florida and willing to relocate

Profile

Plug-and-play full stack web developer with over 12 years of experience building websites, applications, API, chatbots, and prototypes.

Spent the last 6 years leading and mentoring web and mobile engineering teams, remotely and physically, at digital marketing agencies, working for high-profile clients with demanding features, deadlines, and budgets.

Currently seeking for a technical position to move away from the management path. Extremely enthusiastic about learning and optimizing workflows, user experience, deployment processes, communication, collaboration, app performance, and staff satisfaction.

Professional Experience

M8 Director of Technology August 2016 - Present ➤ Miami, FL

- Lead technical point-of-contact for all clients.
- Hire, manage and mentor engineering teams onsite and remotely.
- Develop and present prototypes to introduce new capabilities, such as AI,
 NLP, chatbots, Alexa skills, beacons, and video intelligence.
- Improve web development quality and efficiency by introducing agile processes, best practices, modern workflows, and tools.
- Regularly involved in day-to-day web development tasks for internal and client projects.

Nobox Director of Technology & Partner

March 2011 - July 2016 \blacktriangleright Miami, FL

- Served as the technical point-of-contact for all clients.
- · Hired, managed and mentored an on-site web development team.
- Developed internal products for media trafficking, social listening, automagic asset preparation, and collaboration.
- Occasionally involved in day-to-day web development tasks for internal and client projects.
- Responsible for budgeting and estimation of technical projects.
- Developed web applications used by millions of users for clients such as Sony PlayStation, Mozilla Firefox, Marriott and Copa Airlines.

Kolapse Interactive CTO & Co-Founder

February 2008 - March 2011 ▶ San Juan, PR

University of Puerto Rico Lead Web Developer

August 2004 - December 2010 ▶ San Juan, PR

Core Skills

JavaScript, PHP, CSS3, HTML5, MySQL, Git, terminal, Node.js, React, jQuery, Angular, Laravel, Express, SASS, APIs, oAuth, prototyping, debugging, staff mentoring and development, empathy-driven communication and collaboration, adaptability, addiction to learning, team player, creative and critical thinking, budgetting and estimation

Education

University of Puerto Rico, Rio Piedras Computer Science, General Science 2003 - 2008

Languages

Native bilingual proficiency in English and Spanish.

Interests

video games, podcasts, web development, personal computing, parenting, basketball, movies, philosophy, cooking, eating, bourbons, guitar playing, writing, music

Contact

(305) 588-4688 antoniwan@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/antoniwan www.arod.us